Associated Students of Duke University Records, 1965 - 1991 UA.31.02.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Financial Materials, 1968-1990; 2
  - Student Organizations--Audits, 1980-1981 (Box 26)
  - Student Organizations--Audits, 1981-1982 (Box 26)
  - Legal Services Fees, 1980-1983 (Box 27)
  - Audits, 1981-1982 (Box 27)
  - Student Organizations--Budget Requets, 1982-1983 (Box 27)
  - Student Organizations--Audits, 1982-1983 (Box 27)
  - ASDU Executive Budget, 1983-1991 (Box 27)
  - Budget Requests, 1982-1983 (Box 27)
  - Budgets Returned, 1982-1983 (Box 27)
  - Final Budgets, 1982-1983 (Box 27)
  - Club Audits, 1982-1983 (Box 28)
  - Budgets, 1982-1984 (Box 28)
  - Budget Requests, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
  - Budgets, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
  - Executive Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
  - Student Organizations Committee Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
  - Student Organizations, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
  - FAC Steering Committee Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
  - Line-Item Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
  - Approved Budgets, 1 of 2, 1983-1984 (Box 29)
  - Approved Budgets, 2 of 2, 1983-1984 (Box 29)
  - Audits, 1983-1984 (Box 29)
  - Budget Packets, 1984-1985 (Box 29)
  - Audits: Line Items, 1983-1984 (Box 29)
  - MISC Budget Info, 1983-1984 (Box 29)
  - Budget Recommendations, 1 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 29)
  - Budget Recommendations, 2 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 30)
  - Student Organizations--Income Statements, 1984-1985 (Box 30)
  - Student Organizations-- Budget Requests, 1984-1985 (Box 30)
  - ASDU General Journal (Buisness Manager), 1984-1985 (Box 30)
  - Packets, 1 of 3, 1984-1985 (Box 30)
  - Packets, 2 of 3, 1984-1985 (Box 30)
  - Packets, 3 of 3, 1984-1985 (Box 30)
  - Student Organizations--Budgets, 1985-1986 (Box 30)
  - Student Organizations--Income Statements, 1985-1986 (Box 30)
  - Programming Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 30)
  - Budgets, 1985-1986 (Box 30)
  - Insurance, 1982-1986 (Box 31)
  - Programming Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 31)
  - Budget Meetings, 1985 September 22 (Box 31)
  - Budget Meetings, 1985 September 24 (Box 31)
  - Budget Meetings, 1985 September 29 (Box 31)
    Women's Group; International Association; Programming Fund; Chance
  - Budget Meetings, 1985 October 1 (Box 31)
    College Bowl; ASME; Young Democratsl ART Union, PPS MU, Programming Fund
  - Budget Meetings, 1985 October 6 (Box 31)
  - Budget Meetings, 1985 October 8 (Box 31)
    Outing Club; CHANCE; Programming Fund
  - Budget Meetings, 1985 October 10 (Box 31)
    Hoof 'n' Horn; APO; Project Wild; PPS MU
  - Budget Meetings, 1985 October 20 (Box 31)
  - Budget Meetings, 1985 October 22 (Box 31)
    Women's Group; International Association;Programming Fund;Chance
  - Budget Meetings, 1985 November 3 (Box 31)
    Dance; Ropes; IA; Africa Initiative; AIESEC; P.F.; Coffeehouse; SAMS (Students Against Multiple Scolerosis)
  - MISC Budgets, 1986 (Box 31)
    Durham Education Volunteers; German; D.C.M.; Duke Companions; DRAGO
  - Student Organizations--Budgeting Workshops, 1986-1987 (Box 31)
    ECOS; SBE; Italian Club; French Club; DMEU; Project Wild; NC Student Leg; Hillel; Geology
  - Student Organizations--Allocations, 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - Miscellanous Budgets, 1982-1986 (Box 31)
  - Miscellanous Budgets, 1985-1986 (Box 31)
  - Sports Clubs Budgets, 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - SARC Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 32)
  - Programming Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 32)
  - SoC, 1986 (Box 32)
  - Budget Meetings, 1986 September 25 (Box 32)
  - Budget Meetings, 1986 October 1 (Box 32)
  - Budget Meetings, 1986 October 2 (Box 32)
    Duke Guide; DIPEC
  - Budget Meetings, 1986 October 12 (Box 32)
    Chance; Arnold Air Society; Outing Club; Bench+Bar
  - Budget Meetings, 1986 October 15 (Box 32)
    Aghanistan Action Committee; Asian Students Association; Duke Dance; Bravo! Committee; AIESEC
  - Budget Meetings, 1986 October 23 (Box 32)
    Russian Club; Students for America; South Asian Assoc; WOODS
  - Budget Meetings, 1986 October 26 (Box 32)
    IEEE; Buisness Endeavors Association; College Bowl; Coffeehouse
  - Budget Meetings, 1986 November 2 (Box 32)
    Art Majors Union; Programming Fund; Marine Lab Club; Duke Democrats
  - Budget Meetings, 1986 November 12 (Box 32)
    ECOS; Women's Center; SALSA; Publications Board; ASDU Exec
  - Budget Meetings, 1986 November 19 (Box 32)
    Duke Homeless Project; Int'l Assoc; Ropes Couse; ASCE; Latent Image; Hoof 'n' Horn
  - Budget Meetings, 1986 December 3 (Box 32)
    Duke Homeless Project; TCEB; Hillel; ASME
  - Budget Meetings, 1987 January 21 (Box 32)
    SETA; ASME; Duke-Africa Initative; DUVS; CHANCE
  - Budget Meetings, 1987 February 5 (Box 32)
    Comparative Area Studies Majors' Union, Programming Fund; Chanticleer; Soc. Of Black Engineers
  - Budget Meetings, 1987 February 12-15 (Box 32)
    Programming Fund; Pol. Sci Majors Union
  - Budget Meetings, 1987 February 19 (Box 32)
    PISCES; DGLA
  - Budget Meetings, 1987 February 26 (Box 32)
  - Budget Meetings, 1987 March 1 (Box 32)
  - Budget Meetings, 1987 March 3 (Box 32)
  - Budget Meetings, 1987 March 16 (Box 32)
  - Budget Meetings, 1987 March 19 (Box 32)
  - Line-Iten Budget Requests, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
  - Budget Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
  - Sports Clubs (SCC-Sports Club Council), 1987-1989 (Box 33)
  - Student Organizations--Allocations, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
  - SARC Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
  - Student Organizations--Allocations, 1988-1989 (Box 33)
  - ASDU Executive Budget, 1988 (Box 33)
  - Budget Meetings, 1988 September 13 (Box 33)
  - Budget Meetings, 1988 September 22 (Box 33)
  - Budget Meetings, 1988 September 29 (Box 33)
    Archive; Chanticleer; PICAD; CHANCE
  - Budget Meetings, 1988 October 4 (Box 33)
    Arnold Air Society; Coffeehouse; Hoof 'n' Horn; Duke Aviators; Italian Club; PICES; Duke Dems
  - Budget Meetings, 1988 October 13 (Box 33)
    Psychology Club; ASME; Arnold Air Society; AIESEC
  - Budget Meetings, 1988 October 20 (Box 33)
    SALSA; Arnold Air Society; Wesley Fellowship, IEEE; AISEC; Psychology Club; Homeless Project
  - Budget Meetings, 1988 November 3 (Box 33)
    Music Association; Volunteers for Youth; French Club; Campus Crusade; Wesley Fellowship
  - Transfer Advisory Council, 1982-1988 (Box 34)
    ECOS; Duke Blue; Duke Companions; Asian Student Association; SALSA
  - Residential Program Funding Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
    CASC; Safewalks; Rape Task Force; Duke Companions; Alspaugh; PPS Majors Union; Baptist Student Union; ASA
  - Programming Fund, 1989 (Box 34)
    Lancaster Language House
  - ASDU Executive, 1989 (Box 34)
  - Budget Meetings, 1988 November 10 (Box 34)
    AIESEC; N.C. Rural Health Coalition; Habitat for Humanity; College Bowl
  - Budget Meetings, 1988 November 17 (Box 34)
    Presbyterian Fellowship; Ace of Hearts; Catholic Student Center; Bridge Club; WOODS; Student Committee for Study Abroad;Outing Club; Student-Faculty Service Project
  - Budget Meetings, 1988 December 1 (Box 34)
    CSN; BSA; Youth Outreach; Marine Lab Club; Catholic Student Center
  - Programming Fund, 1988-1990 (Box 34)
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 January 2 (Box 34)
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 January 26 (Box 34)
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 February 2 (Box 34)
    Hats Off!; Religious Life Bylaw; Alspaugh, Int'l Assoc: Comp. Area Studies; P.U.S.H.
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 February 9 (Box 34)
    Wind Symphony
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 February 12 (Box 34)
    Comp Area Studies; SCC; ASDU
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 February 16 (Box 34)
    SALSA; SAC Week; DELA; Women's Coalition; SALAP; CCC
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 February 19 (Box 34)
    Publications Board; FAC
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 February 23 (Box 34)
    SAC; WXDU;FAC; Pub Board
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 March 2 (Box 34)
    WXDU; ASDU Exec
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 March 9 (Box 34)
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 March 21 (Box 34)
    ASDU Exec; SARC
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 March 23 (Box 34)
    BSA
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 March 30 (Box 34)
    Pub Board; SALAP
  - Budget Meetings, 1989 April 6 (Box 34)
    Comparative Area Studies Majors; Duke India Association; BSA
  - MISC Budgets (Box 35)
  - MISC Line-Items Info (Box 35)
- Committees, 1965-1991; 3
  The Committees series features minutes, reports, memorandum and notes compiled by ASDU committees. The ASDU Committees subseries contains the materials of committees ASDU commissioned to study an aspect of Duke undergraduate life such as financial aid, dining services, and alcohol awareness. The University Committees subseries includes the records of ASDU student representatives who served on university wide committees such as the Academic Council and Residence Life Committee. The Board of Trustees subseries consists of the records of the ASDU representative to the Board of Trustees. The Athletic Council subseries includes ASDU copies of materials produced by this influential university committee.
  - ASDU Committees, 1972-1990; 3_1
    The ASDU Committees subseries contains the records of student committees. ASDU sponsored both standing committees such as the Academic Affairs Committee and task forces to study pressing issues such as the Task Force on Black-White Relations. The committees were usually run by ASDU officers but were also staffed by members of the general student body and task forces often appointed representatives from student groups involved with the issue studied. The committees often produced a report for the ASDU Executive Council and Duke officials summarizing the findings of the committee and suggesting future recommendations.
    - ASDU Committees--lists, 1972-1973; 1980-1981 (Box 35)
    - Committee Review Board, 1974-1980 (Box 35)
    - ASDU Implementation Reports, 1982 (Box 35)
    - Academic Affairs, 1980-1981 (Box 35)
    - Academic Affairs, 1984-1986 (Box 35)
    - Academic Affairs: Report, 1988 (Box 35)
    - Academic Affairs: Joint Meetings with Student Affairs, 1984 (Box 35)
    - Academic Standards Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 35)
    - Accrediation Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 35)
    - Alcohol Awareness Task Force, 1981-1982 (Box 35)
    - Alcohol Awareness Task Force, 1981-1984 (Box 35)
    - Alcohol Awareness Task Force, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Alcohol Policy Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 35)
    - Alcohol Policy Committee: Drinking Age, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Alcoholic Beverages Regulations Review Committee, 1990 (Box 36)
    - Alumni Affairs Committee, 1985 (Box 36)
    - Alumni Affairs Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 36)
    - Athletics, 1975-1976 (Box 36)
    - Atheltic Affairs Committee, 1975-1980 (Box 36)
    - Athletic Affairs Committee, 1976 (Box 36)
    - Athletic Affairs + Maintainence, 1980-1981 (Box 36)
    - Athletic Affairs Committee: Student Problems (Box 36)
    - Atheltic Affairs Committee: Study Survey, 1982 (Box 36)
    - Task Force on Black Studies, 1975 (Box 36)
    - Task Force on Black-White Relations, 1 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 36)
    - Task Force on Black-White Relations, 2 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 36)
    - Black on White Steering Committees, 1981 (Box 37)
    - Ad Hoc Budget Committee, 1975 (Box 37)
    - Budget Commission, 1975-1977 (Box 37)
    - Committee Interview Forms, 1970-1971 (Box 37)
    - Committee on Consitutional Review, 1 of 2, 1986-1991 (Box 37)
    - Committee on Constitutional Review, 2 of 2, 1986-1991 (Box 37)
    - Counseling + Psychological Services (CAPS) Student Advisory Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 37)
    - Defunct Committees, 1972-1978 (Box 37)
    - Curriculum Review Committee, 1983 (Box 37)
    - Task Force on Dining Halls, 1979 (Box 37)
    - Dining Halls Task Force, 1980-1982 (Box 37)
    - Dining Halls Task Force, 1985-1987 (Box 37)
    - Committee for Enhancement of East Campus Athletic Facilities, 1985 (Box 37)
    - Elections Commission, 1980 (Box 38)
    - Energy Awareness Task Force, 1981 (Box 38)
    - Energy Conservation Committee, 1977 (Box 38)
    - External Affairs, 1979-1980 (Box 38)
    - External Affairs, 1985 (Box 38)
    - Financial Aid Task Force, 1975-1977 (Box 38)
    - Financial Aid Task Force, 1982 (Box 38)
    - Task Force on Fire Safety, 1981 (Box 38)
    - Graduate Student Committee, 1981 (Box 38)
    - Task Force on Institutional Advancement, 1981 (Box 38)
    - Handicapped Student Committee, 1978 (Box 38)
    - Judicial Review Board, 1974-1980 (Box 38)
    - Judicial Affairs Committee, 1974 (Box 38)
    - Judicial Review Board, 1977-1988 (Box 38)
    - Judicial Review Committee, 1977-1985 (Box 38)
    - Judicial Review Committee, 1987 (Box 38)
    - Judicial Review Committee: Interim Report, 1977 (Box 38)
    - Task Force on Judicial System, 1978 (Box 38)
    - Task Force on Grounds, 1986-1988 (Box 39)
    - Grounds Committee: Panhellenic Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 39)
    - Grounds Committee: Bench Policy, 1988 (Box 39)
    - Grounds Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 39)
    - Task Force on Legislative Revision, undated (Box 39)
    - Legislative Committee, 1977-1982 (Box 39)
    - Commission on Organizational Reform, 1983 (Box 39)
    - Orientation Committee, 1985 (Box 39)
    - Parking Task Force, 1988 (Box 39)
    - Public Relations Committee, 1985 (Box 39)
    - Retrenchment Committee-Response to Directions for Progress, 1980 (Box 39)
    - Schedule Committee, 1974-1977 (Box 39)
    - Sports Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 39)
    - Student Affairs Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 39)
    - Tenure Study Commission, 1975 (Box 39)
    - University Affairs, 1981 (Box 39)
    - University Governance, 1975-1976 (Box 39)
    - University Governance: Report, 1975 (Box 39)
    - University Governance:Report, 1976 (Box 39)
    - University Governance: Development Governance, undated (Box 39)
    - University Governance, 1976 (Box 40)
    - University Union Board Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 40)
    - Student Life Committee, 1977-1985 (Box 40)
    - Young Trustee Committee, 1989 (Box 40)
  - University Committees, 1966-1991; 3_2
    The University Committees subseries features the records of student members of official Duke University committees between 1965-1991. Duke undergraduates could apply to serve as ASDU representatives on committees such as the Student Affairs Trustee Committee and the Undergraduate Faculty Committee of Arts and Sciences (UFCAS). The representatives were expected to file a monthly update with the ASDU offices. Materials include meeting minutes, agendas, memorandum and official committee reports.
    - University Committees-lists, 1971-1974 (Box 40)
    - Academic Council, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Academic Council: Graduate School, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Academic Council, 1979 (Box 40)
    - Academic Council: Freshman Clusters, 1982 (Box 40)
    - Academic Council, 1984 (Box 40)
    - Academic Council, 1984-1986 (Box 40)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Campus Counseling, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Committee on Career Counseling Services, 1977 (Box 40)
    - Committee on Computing, 1989 (Box 40)
    - Chancellor's Advisory Committee: Faculty Fundraising, 1979 (Box 40)
    - Chancellor's Applied Committee: Instruction in the Arts, undated (Box 40)
    - Council on the Applied Arts, 1977-1979 (Box 41)
    - Commission on the Arts, 1976 (Box 41)
    - Campaign for the Arts, Sciences, Engineering, 1987 (Box 41)
    - Council on Undergrad Affairs, 1990 (Box 41)
    - Central Campus Study Committee, 1983-1987 (Box 41)
    - Committee on Educational Policy and Programs, 1980 (Box 41)
    - Council on the Role of East Campus, undated (Box 41)
    - Federations Task Force, 1982 (Box 41)
    - Federations, 1982 (Box 41)
    - Health Science Education Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Intramurals Committee, 1965-1976 (Box 41)
    - Recreation Facility Task Force, 1990 (Box 41)
    - Residential Life Committee (RLC), 1973-1974 (Box 41)
    - Residential Life Committee: Proposals, Reports, Questionnaires, 1972-1975 (Box 42)
    - Residential Life Committee: Proposals, 1972-1979 (Box 42)
    - Residence Life: Minutes, 1975-1979 (Box 42)
    - Residence Life: Housing Study, 1976 (Box 42)
    - Residence Life: Implementing Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 42)
    - Residence Life: Residential Colleges, 1984 (Box 42)
    - Residence Life: Residential Commons Task Force, 1984 (Box 42)
    - Residential Life: Presidential Committee, 1984 (Box 42)
    - Residence Life, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Residence Life Task Force, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Residence Life: East Campus, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Residence Life Task Force: Overenrollment (Box 43)
    - Residence Life: Facilities and Rennovation, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Residence LifeL Overcrowding, 1984-1991 (Box 43)
    - Search Committee, 1976 (Box 43)
    - Search Committee, Special, 1978-1981 (Box 43)
    - Special Advisory Search Committee, 1978 (Box 43)
    - Special Committee on Educational Policy and Programs, Trinity College (Box 43)
    - Special 50th Anniversary Committee, 1980 (Box 43)
    - Search Committee: Student Affairs (Box 43)
    - Student Affairs Trustee Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 43)
    - SFAC Records, 1966-1967 (Box 43)
    - SFAC Records, 1967-1968 (Box 43)
    - Student Health Advisory Board, 1976 (Box 43)
    - Traffic Commission, 1973-1978 (Box 44)
    - Teaching Awards Selection Committtee, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Task Force on Technology in the Registration Process, 1990 (Box 44)
    - Telephone Registration Policy Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 44)
    - Urban Land Institute Study Committeee, 1986 (Box 44)
    - University Budget Committee, 1977 (Box 44)
    - University Union Committee, 1971 (Box 44)
    - Task Force on University Governance, 1988 (Box 44)
    - University Investment Committtee, 1978 (Box 44)
    - UFCAS: Guide, 1984-1989 (Box 44)
    - UFCAS Review, 1982 (Box 44)
    - UFCAS, 1974-1975 (Box 45)
    - UFCAS, 1974-1979 (Box 45)
    - UFCAS, 1977 (Box 45)
    - UFCAS, 1977-1981 (Box 45)
    - UFCAS, 1 of 2, 1978 (Box 45)
    - UFCAS, 2 of 2, 1978 (Box 45)
    - UFCAS, 1979 (Box 45)
    - UFCAS, 1980 (Box 46)
    - UFCAS, 1 of 2, 1983-1988 (Box 46)
    - UFCAS, 2 of 2, 1983-1988 (Box 46)
    - UFCAS: Academic Standards Committee, 1990 (Box 46)
    - UFCAS: Committee on Admissions and Financial Aid, 1973-1978 (Box 46)
    - UFCAS: Committee on Admissions and Financial Aid: Financial Aid Budget Study, 1976 (Box 46)
    - UFCAS: Committee on Admissions and Financial Aid: recommendations, 1978 (Box 46)
    - UFCAS: Committee on Admissions and Financial Aid: Trinity College Admissions report, 1978 (Box 46)
    - UFCAS: Admissions and Financial Aid Committee, 1972-1978 (Box 47)
    - UFCAS: Admissions and Financial Aid Committee, 1980 (Box 47)
    - UFCAS: Admissions and Financial Aid Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 47)
    - UFCAS: Admissions, Tuition and Financial Aid, 1979-1980 (Box 47)
    - UFCAS: Admissions and Financial Aid Committee, 1984 (Box 47)
    - UFCAS: Admissions, 1986 (Box 47)
    - UFCAS: Advising Committee, Survey, 1978-1979 (Box 47)
    - UFCAS: Advising Committee, 1982-1989 (Box 47)
    - AFCAS: Advising, 1988 (Box 47)
    - UFCAS: Advising Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 47)
    - UFCAS: Angier B. Duke Scholarship, 1978 (Box 47)
    - UFCAS: Committee on Courses of Instruction, 1978 (Box 47)
    - UFCAS: Committee on Courses of Instruction, 1977-1979 (Box 47)
  - Board of Trustees, 1968-1984; 3_3
    Conditions Governing Access
    Trustee records: Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been in existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1972-1975 (Box 48)
      Restricted until 2025.
    - Executive Committee Meeting, August 23, 1974 (Box 48)
      Restricted until 2024.
    - Executive Committee Meeting, November 1, 1974 (Box 48)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, December 7, 1974 (Box 48)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, January 17, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, March 6, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, March 7, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, April; 1975 (Box 48)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 9-10, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 13, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, July 18, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, August 22, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, September 26-27, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, November 7, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, December 12-13, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, January 16, 1976 (Box 48)
      Restricted until 2026.
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, March 5-6, 1976 (Box 48)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, April 9, 1976 (Box 49)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 11, 1976 (Box 49)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, July 16, 1976 (Box 49)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, August 20, 1976 (Box 49)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, September 24-25, 1976 (Box 49)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, December 10-11, 1976 (Box 49)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, January 14, 1977 (Box 49)
      Restricted until 2027.
    - Executive Committee Meeting, April 1, 1977 (Box 49)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 6-7, 1977 (Box 49)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 10, 1977 (Box 49)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, July 15, 1977 (Box 49)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, September 23-24, 1977 (Box 49)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, November 4, 1977 (Box 49)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, December 9-10, 1977 (Box 49)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, January 13, 1978 (Box 49)
      Restricted until 2028.
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1978 February 25 (Box 49)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, March 3, 1978 (Box 49)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 5-7, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 9, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, July 14, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, September 29-30, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, November 3, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, December 8-9, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, November 6, 1981 (Box 50)
      Restricted until 2031.
    - Executive Committee Meeting, January 16, 1981 (Box 50)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1981 February 27-28 (Box 50)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, April 3, 1981 (Box 50)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 8-9, 1981 (Box 50)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 12, 1981 (Box 50)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, September 25-26, 1981 (Box 50)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, January 25, 1985 (Box 50)
      Restricted until 2035.
    - Buisness and Finance Committee Communication, 1970-1974 (Box 50)
    - MISC Board of Trustees Materials, 1 of 3, 1982 (Box 50)
      Restricted until 2032.
    - MISC Board of Trustees Materials, 2 of 3, 1978 (Box 50)
    - MISC Board of Trustees Materials, 3 of 3, 1978 (Box 51)
    - Institutional Advancement, ca 1972-1978 (Box 51)
    - Operating Budget, 1985-1987 (Box 51)
      Restricted until 2037.
    - Tuition, 1986 (Box 51)
      Restricted until 2036.
    - Proposal to Trustees, 1968 (Box 51)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 51)
      Restricted until 2034.
  - Athletic Council, 1972; 1982; 3_4
    The Athletic Council subseries contains select records from the Athletic Council which oversaw Duke intercollegiate and club athletics. The subseries contains a series of 1972 surveys distributed to student athletes from Duke's 10 Division I intercollegiate athletic programs. The subseries also contain a 1982 report, "Recommendations on Intercollegiate Athletics", analyzes and proposes plans for the future of Duke sports teams.
    - DUAC Questionnaires- Baseball, 1972 (Box 52)
      Restricted until 2042.
    - DUAC Questionnaires-Basketball, 1972 (Box 52)
    - DUAC Questionnaires-Football, 1972 (Box 52)
    - DUAC Questionnaires-Fencing, 1972 (Box 52)
    - DUAC Questionnaires-Golf, 1972 (Box 52)